{
    "EE6405_W10_ A survey of NLP applications across diverse industries_For Students.pdf": {
        "EE6405": [
            {
                "text": "Simon Liu",
                "label": "PERSON",
                "page_num": [
                    1
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "NTU Electrical and Electronic Engineering",
                "label": "ORG",
                "page_num": [
                    1
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "2023",
                "label": "DATE",
                "page_num": [
                    1
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "Nanyang Technological University",
                "label": "ORG",
                "page_num": [
                    1
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "Singapore",
                "label": "GPE",
                "page_num": [
                    1
                ]
            }
        ],
        "A Survey of NLP Applications": [
            {
                "text": "2023",
                "label": "DATE",
                "page_num": [
                    2
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "Nanyang Technological University",
                "label": "ORG",
                "page_num": [
                    2
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "Singapore",
                "label": "GPE",
                "page_num": [
                    2
                ]
            }
        ],
        "Overview": [
            {
                "text": "NLP",
                "label": "ORG",
                "page_num": [
                    3
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "Healthcare",
                "label": "ORG",
                "page_num": [
                    3
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "Hospitality",
                "label": "PERSON",
                "page_num": [
                    3
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "Entertainment\nGovernment",
                "label": "ORG",
                "page_num": [
                    3
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "Nanyang Technological University",
                "label": "ORG",
                "page_num": [
                    3
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "Singapore",
                "label": "GPE",
                "page_num": [
                    3
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "3",
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "page_num": [
                    3
                ]
            }
        ],
        "Healthcare": [
            {
                "text": "Healthcare",
                "label": "ORG",
                "page_num": [
                    4,
                    5
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "Discovery",
                "label": "PRODUCT",
                "page_num": [
                    4
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "• Analyzes",
                "label": "ORG",
                "page_num": [
                    4
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "• Mines",
                "label": "PRODUCT",
                "page_num": [
                    4
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "•\n Integrates",
                "label": "ORG",
                "page_num": [
                    4
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "• Speeds",
                "label": "PRODUCT",
                "page_num": [
                    4
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "2023",
                "label": "DATE",
                "page_num": [
                    4,
                    5
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "Nanyang Technological University",
                "label": "ORG",
                "page_num": [
                    4,
                    5
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "Singapore",
                "label": "GPE",
                "page_num": [
                    4,
                    5
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "4",
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "page_num": [
                    4
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "▪ IBM Watson Health \n▪ Company Profile",
                "label": "ORG",
                "page_num": [
                    5
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "Mayo Clinic",
                "label": "ORG",
                "page_num": [
                    5
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "Sloan Kettering",
                "label": "PERSON",
                "page_num": [
                    5
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "▪ Epic Systems",
                "label": "ORG",
                "page_num": [
                    5
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "Cleveland Clinic",
                "label": "ORG",
                "page_num": [
                    5
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "Johns Hopkins",
                "label": "ORG",
                "page_num": [
                    5
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "5",
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "page_num": [
                    5
                ]
            }
        ],
        "Finance and Banking": [
            {
                "text": "Banking\nFinancial Report \nAutomation\nFraud\nDetection\nCustomer Service",
                "label": "ORG",
                "page_num": [
                    6
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "Chatbots",
                "label": "PRODUCT",
                "page_num": [
                    6
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "• Automates",
                "label": "ORG",
                "page_num": [
                    6,
                    6
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "•\nIdentifies",
                "label": "ORG",
                "page_num": [
                    6
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "2023",
                "label": "DATE",
                "page_num": [
                    6,
                    7
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "Nanyang Technological University",
                "label": "ORG",
                "page_num": [
                    6,
                    7
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "Singapore",
                "label": "GPE",
                "page_num": [
                    6,
                    7
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "6",
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "page_num": [
                    6
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "AI",
                "label": "ORG",
                "page_num": [
                    7
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "Goldman Sachs",
                "label": "ORG",
                "page_num": [
                    7
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "J.P. Morgan",
                "label": "ORG",
                "page_num": [
                    7
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "Société Générale",
                "label": "PERSON",
                "page_num": [
                    7
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "Credit Agricole",
                "label": "ORG",
                "page_num": [
                    7
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "7",
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "page_num": [
                    7
                ]
            }
        ],
        "Retail and E-Commerce": [
            {
                "text": "▪ Informs",
                "label": "ORG",
                "page_num": [
                    8
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "▪ Personalized Recommendations",
                "label": "ORG",
                "page_num": [
                    8
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "▪ Increases",
                "label": "ORG",
                "page_num": [
                    8
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "▪ Customer Service Chatbots",
                "label": "ORG",
                "page_num": [
                    8
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "▪ Automates",
                "label": "GPE",
                "page_num": [
                    8
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "2023",
                "label": "DATE",
                "page_num": [
                    8,
                    9
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "Nanyang Technological University",
                "label": "ORG",
                "page_num": [
                    8,
                    9
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "Singapore",
                "label": "GPE",
                "page_num": [
                    8,
                    9
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "8",
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "page_num": [
                    8
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "Dell",
                "label": "ORG",
                "page_num": [
                    9
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "▪ Algolia\n▪ Company Profile: Search",
                "label": "FAC",
                "page_num": [
                    9
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "9",
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "page_num": [
                    9
                ]
            }
        ],
        "Legal Industry": [
            {
                "text": "Legal Industry\nDocument Review",
                "label": "ORG",
                "page_num": [
                    10
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "Analysis\nPredictive\nAnalysis\nCompliance\nMonitoring\n• Automates",
                "label": "PRODUCT",
                "page_num": [
                    10
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "• Predicts",
                "label": "PRODUCT",
                "page_num": [
                    10
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "• Ensures",
                "label": "PRODUCT",
                "page_num": [
                    10
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "•\nIdentifies",
                "label": "PRODUCT",
                "page_num": [
                    10
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "• Reduces",
                "label": "LOC",
                "page_num": [
                    10
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "2023",
                "label": "DATE",
                "page_num": [
                    10,
                    11
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "Nanyang Technological University",
                "label": "ORG",
                "page_num": [
                    10,
                    11
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "Singapore",
                "label": "GPE",
                "page_num": [
                    10,
                    11
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "10",
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "page_num": [
                    10
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "Legal Industry",
                "label": "ORG",
                "page_num": [
                    11
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "AI",
                "label": "ORG",
                "page_num": [
                    11
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "Lex Machina",
                "label": "PERSON",
                "page_num": [
                    11
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "Google",
                "label": "ORG",
                "page_num": [
                    11
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "Microsoft",
                "label": "ORG",
                "page_num": [
                    11
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "11",
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "page_num": [
                    11
                ]
            }
        ],
        "Automotive Industry": [
            {
                "text": "Automotive Industry\n▪ Voice-Activated Assistants\n▪ Enhances",
                "label": "ORG",
                "page_num": [
                    12
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "▪ Gains",
                "label": "WORK_OF_ART",
                "page_num": [
                    12
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "▪ Informs",
                "label": "ORG",
                "page_num": [
                    12
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "2023",
                "label": "DATE",
                "page_num": [
                    12,
                    13
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "Nanyang Technological University",
                "label": "ORG",
                "page_num": [
                    12,
                    13
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "Singapore",
                "label": "GPE",
                "page_num": [
                    12,
                    13
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "12",
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "page_num": [
                    12
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "Automotive Industry\n▪ Nuance Dragon Drive",
                "label": "ORG",
                "page_num": [
                    13
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "Audi",
                "label": "ORG",
                "page_num": [
                    13
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "BMW",
                "label": "ORG",
                "page_num": [
                    13
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "SoundHound",
                "label": "ORG",
                "page_num": [
                    13
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "Houndify\n▪ Company Profile",
                "label": "ORG",
                "page_num": [
                    13
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "Mercedes-Benz",
                "label": "ORG",
                "page_num": [
                    13
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "Hyundai",
                "label": "ORG",
                "page_num": [
                    13
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "13",
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "page_num": [
                    13
                ]
            }
        ],
        "Publishing Industry": [
            {
                "text": "Publishing Industry",
                "label": "ORG",
                "page_num": [
                    14,
                    15
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "▪ Enhances",
                "label": "ORG",
                "page_num": [
                    14
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "2023",
                "label": "DATE",
                "page_num": [
                    14,
                    15
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "Nanyang Technological University",
                "label": "ORG",
                "page_num": [
                    14,
                    15
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "Singapore",
                "label": "GPE",
                "page_num": [
                    14,
                    15
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "14",
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "page_num": [
                    14
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "GPT-3\n▪ Company Profile",
                "label": "ORG",
                "page_num": [
                    15
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "▪ Narrativa\n▪ Company Profile",
                "label": "ORG",
                "page_num": [
                    15
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "Associated Press",
                "label": "ORG",
                "page_num": [
                    15
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "Yahoo",
                "label": "ORG",
                "page_num": [
                    15
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "15",
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "page_num": [
                    15
                ]
            }
        ],
        "Education": [
            {
                "text": "▪ Adapts",
                "label": "PERSON",
                "page_num": [
                    16
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "Language Learning Tools\n▪ Assists",
                "label": "WORK_OF_ART",
                "page_num": [
                    16
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "▪ Offers",
                "label": "ORG",
                "page_num": [
                    16
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "2023",
                "label": "DATE",
                "page_num": [
                    16,
                    17
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "Nanyang Technological University",
                "label": "ORG",
                "page_num": [
                    16,
                    17
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "Singapore",
                "label": "GPE",
                "page_num": [
                    16,
                    17
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "16",
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "page_num": [
                    16
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "Harvard",
                "label": "ORG",
                "page_num": [
                    17
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "Oxford",
                "label": "ORG",
                "page_num": [
                    17
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "▪ Grammarly\n▪ Company Profile",
                "label": "FAC",
                "page_num": [
                    17
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "Grammar",
                "label": "PERSON",
                "page_num": [
                    17
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "17",
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "page_num": [
                    17
                ]
            }
        ],
        "Travel and Hospitality": [
            {
                "text": "Hospitality\n▪ Automated Booking Assistants\n",
                "label": "ORG",
                "page_num": [
                    18
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "▪ Simplifies",
                "label": "ORG",
                "page_num": [
                    18
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "▪ Offers",
                "label": "ORG",
                "page_num": [
                    18
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "▪ Customer Feedback Analysis",
                "label": "ORG",
                "page_num": [
                    18
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "▪ Enhances",
                "label": "ORG",
                "page_num": [
                    18
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "2023",
                "label": "DATE",
                "page_num": [
                    18,
                    19
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "Nanyang Technological University",
                "label": "ORG",
                "page_num": [
                    18,
                    19
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "Singapore",
                "label": "GPE",
                "page_num": [
                    18,
                    19
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "18",
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "page_num": [
                    18
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "Hospitality\n▪ Amadeus\n▪ Company Profile: Travel",
                "label": "ORG",
                "page_num": [
                    19
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "British Airways",
                "label": "ORG",
                "page_num": [
                    19
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "Expedia",
                "label": "GPE",
                "page_num": [
                    19
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "Booking.com Chatbot\n▪ Company Profile",
                "label": "ORG",
                "page_num": [
                    19
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "Global Booking.com",
                "label": "ORG",
                "page_num": [
                    19
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "19",
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "page_num": [
                    19
                ]
            }
        ],
        "Media and Entertainment": [
            {
                "text": "Media and Entertainment\n▪ Content Recommendation Systems",
                "label": "ORG",
                "page_num": [
                    20
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "▪ Personalizes",
                "label": "ORG",
                "page_num": [
                    20
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "▪ Increases",
                "label": "WORK_OF_ART",
                "page_num": [
                    20
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "▪ Enhances",
                "label": "ORG",
                "page_num": [
                    20
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "Social Media\n▪ Analyzes",
                "label": "ORG",
                "page_num": [
                    20
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "▪ Informs",
                "label": "ORG",
                "page_num": [
                    20
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "2023",
                "label": "DATE",
                "page_num": [
                    20,
                    21
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "Nanyang Technological University",
                "label": "ORG",
                "page_num": [
                    20,
                    21
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "Singapore",
                "label": "GPE",
                "page_num": [
                    20,
                    21
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "20",
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "page_num": [
                    20
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "Media and Entertainment\n▪ Netflix\n▪ Company Profile",
                "label": "ORG",
                "page_num": [
                    21
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "Valossa\n▪ Company Profile",
                "label": "ORG",
                "page_num": [
                    21
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "Finnish Broadcasting Company",
                "label": "ORG",
                "page_num": [
                    21
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "France",
                "label": "GPE",
                "page_num": [
                    21
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "21",
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "page_num": [
                    21
                ]
            }
        ],
        "Government & Public Sector": [
            {
                "text": "Government & Public Sector\n▪ Public Sentiment Analysis\n▪ Analyzes",
                "label": "ORG",
                "page_num": [
                    22
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "▪ Informs",
                "label": "ORG",
                "page_num": [
                    22
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "▪ Automated Public Services",
                "label": "ORG",
                "page_num": [
                    22
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "Record Management\n▪ Automates",
                "label": "ORG",
                "page_num": [
                    22
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "▪ Facilitates",
                "label": "ORG",
                "page_num": [
                    22
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "2023",
                "label": "DATE",
                "page_num": [
                    22,
                    23
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "Nanyang Technological University",
                "label": "ORG",
                "page_num": [
                    22,
                    23
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "Singapore",
                "label": "GPE",
                "page_num": [
                    22,
                    23
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "22",
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "page_num": [
                    22
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "Government & Public Sector",
                "label": "ORG",
                "page_num": [
                    23
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "Palantir Gotham\n▪",
                "label": "PERSON",
                "page_num": [
                    23
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "U.S. Intelligence, Defense",
                "label": "ORG",
                "page_num": [
                    23
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "U.S. SEC",
                "label": "NORP",
                "page_num": [
                    23
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "UBS",
                "label": "ORG",
                "page_num": [
                    23
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "23",
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "page_num": [
                    23
                ]
            }
        ],
        "Summary": [
            {
                "text": "▪ Customer Engagement\n▪ Enhancing",
                "label": "ORG",
                "page_num": [
                    24
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "2023",
                "label": "DATE",
                "page_num": [
                    24
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "Nanyang Technological University",
                "label": "ORG",
                "page_num": [
                    24
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "Singapore",
                "label": "GPE",
                "page_num": [
                    24
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "24",
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "page_num": [
                    24
                ]
            }
        ]
    },
    "EE6405_W11_ Deep-dive into NLP_For Students.pdf": {
        "EE6405": [
            {
                "text": "Simon Liu",
                "label": "PERSON",
                "page_num": [
                    1
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "NTU Electrical and Electronic Engineering",
                "label": "ORG",
                "page_num": [
                    1
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "2023",
                "label": "DATE",
                "page_num": [
                    1
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "Nanyang Technological University",
                "label": "ORG",
                "page_num": [
                    1
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "Singapore",
                "label": "GPE",
                "page_num": [
                    1
                ]
            }
        ],
        "Deep-dive into": [
            {
                "text": "NLP Applications",
                "label": "ORG",
                "page_num": [
                    2
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "2023",
                "label": "DATE",
                "page_num": [
                    2
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "Nanyang Technological University",
                "label": "ORG",
                "page_num": [
                    2
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "Singapore",
                "label": "GPE",
                "page_num": [
                    2
                ]
            }
        ],
        "Overview": [
            {
                "text": "NLP",
                "label": "ORG",
                "page_num": [
                    3,
                    3
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "ML",
                "label": "ORG",
                "page_num": [
                    3
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "Two",
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "page_num": [
                    3,
                    3
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "▪ Content Moderation\n▪ Product Recommendation Chatbot",
                "label": "WORK_OF_ART",
                "page_num": [
                    3
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "2023",
                "label": "DATE",
                "page_num": [
                    3
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "Nanyang Technological University",
                "label": "ORG",
                "page_num": [
                    3
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "Singapore",
                "label": "GPE",
                "page_num": [
                    3
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "3",
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "page_num": [
                    3
                ]
            }
        ],
        "Fraud Detection Model": [
            {
                "text": "two",
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "page_num": [
                    4
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "Fraud Type\nData Source\nFulfillment Fraud\nProduct",
                "label": "ORG",
                "page_num": [
                    4
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "NLP",
                "label": "ORG",
                "page_num": [
                    4
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "ML",
                "label": "ORG",
                "page_num": [
                    4
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "2023",
                "label": "DATE",
                "page_num": [
                    4
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "Nanyang Technological University",
                "label": "ORG",
                "page_num": [
                    4
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "Singapore",
                "label": "GPE",
                "page_num": [
                    4
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "4",
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "page_num": [
                    4
                ]
            }
        ],
        "Fulfilment Fraud Model": [
            {
                "text": "Model\nSentence \nTransformer",
                "label": "PRODUCT",
                "page_num": [
                    5
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "XGBoost Model",
                "label": "PRODUCT",
                "page_num": [
                    5
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "2023",
                "label": "DATE",
                "page_num": [
                    5,
                    6,
                    7
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "Nanyang Technological University",
                "label": "ORG",
                "page_num": [
                    5,
                    6,
                    7
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "Singapore",
                "label": "GPE",
                "page_num": [
                    5,
                    6,
                    7
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "5",
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "page_num": [
                    5
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "Sentence \nTransformers",
                "label": "PRODUCT",
                "page_num": [
                    6
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "Hugging Face",
                "label": "ORG",
                "page_num": [
                    6
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "512",
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "page_num": [
                    6
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "768",
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "page_num": [
                    6
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "1024",
                "label": "DATE",
                "page_num": [
                    6
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "XGBoost",
                "label": "ORG",
                "page_num": [
                    6,
                    6
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "Model\nSeller \nFeatures",
                "label": "PRODUCT",
                "page_num": [
                    6
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "6",
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "page_num": [
                    6
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "Second",
                "label": "ORDINAL",
                "page_num": [
                    7
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "Seller\nPunishment\nLevel 1 \nReviewer\nLevel 2 \nReviewer\nDownstream Process\n▪ Suspected",
                "label": "WORK_OF_ART",
                "page_num": [
                    7
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "▪ Two",
                "label": "WORK_OF_ART",
                "page_num": [
                    7
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "▪ Confirmed",
                "label": "ORG",
                "page_num": [
                    7
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "7",
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "page_num": [
                    7
                ]
            }
        ],
        "Human Trafficking Model": [
            {
                "text": "Trafficking Model",
                "label": "PERSON",
                "page_num": [
                    8,
                    9,
                    10,
                    12
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "an estimated $150 million",
                "label": "MONEY",
                "page_num": [
                    8
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "annually",
                "label": "DATE",
                "page_num": [
                    8
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "NLP",
                "label": "ORG",
                "page_num": [
                    8
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "ML",
                "label": "ORG",
                "page_num": [
                    8
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "2023",
                "label": "DATE",
                "page_num": [
                    8,
                    9,
                    10,
                    11,
                    12
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "Nanyang Technological University",
                "label": "ORG",
                "page_num": [
                    8,
                    9,
                    10,
                    11,
                    12
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "Singapore",
                "label": "GPE",
                "page_num": [
                    8,
                    9,
                    10,
                    11,
                    12
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "8",
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "page_num": [
                    8
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "KYC",
                "label": "ORG",
                "page_num": [
                    9,
                    10,
                    10
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "Embedding\nClient\nSegmentation \nIsolation Forest",
                "label": "WORK_OF_ART",
                "page_num": [
                    9,
                    10
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "Graph",
                "label": "PERSON",
                "page_num": [
                    9
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "Graph Score\nGraph",
                "label": "ORG",
                "page_num": [
                    9
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "9",
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "page_num": [
                    9
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "Email Money Transfer",
                "label": "WORK_OF_ART",
                "page_num": [
                    10
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "EMT",
                "label": "ORG",
                "page_num": [
                    10
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "▪ Pre",
                "label": "PERSON",
                "page_num": [
                    10
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "BERT",
                "label": "ORG",
                "page_num": [
                    10
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "768",
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "page_num": [
                    10
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "Isolation Forest",
                "label": "ORG",
                "page_num": [
                    10
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "10",
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "page_num": [
                    10
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "Trafficking Model\nSequence",
                "label": "PERSON",
                "page_num": [
                    11
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "▪ Uniform Manifold Approximation and Projection (UMAP",
                "label": "WORK_OF_ART",
                "page_num": [
                    11
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "11",
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "page_num": [
                    11
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "Second",
                "label": "ORDINAL",
                "page_num": [
                    12
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "Human Trafficking\nRisk Score \nOff",
                "label": "WORK_OF_ART",
                "page_num": [
                    12
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "Level 1 \nReviewer\nLevel 2 \nReviewer",
                "label": "PERSON",
                "page_num": [
                    12
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "two",
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "page_num": [
                    12
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "▪ Highly",
                "label": "ORG",
                "page_num": [
                    12
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "12",
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "page_num": [
                    12
                ]
            }
        ],
        "Content Moderation": [
            {
                "text": "2023",
                "label": "DATE",
                "page_num": [
                    13
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "Nanyang Technological University",
                "label": "ORG",
                "page_num": [
                    13
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "Singapore",
                "label": "GPE",
                "page_num": [
                    13
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "13",
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "page_num": [
                    13
                ]
            }
        ],
        "Prohibited Product Example": [
            {
                "text": "1",
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "page_num": [
                    14
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "5",
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "page_num": [
                    14
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "SOP",
                "label": "ORG",
                "page_num": [
                    14
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "2",
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "page_num": [
                    14
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "4",
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "page_num": [
                    14
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "3",
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "page_num": [
                    14
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "2023",
                "label": "DATE",
                "page_num": [
                    14
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "Nanyang Technological University",
                "label": "ORG",
                "page_num": [
                    14
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "Singapore",
                "label": "GPE",
                "page_num": [
                    14
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "14",
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "page_num": [
                    14
                ]
            }
        ],
        "Sequence of Prompts": [
            {
                "text": "Sequence of Prompts\n▪ Provide",
                "label": "ORG",
                "page_num": [
                    15,
                    16
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "▪ Vital",
                "label": "WORK_OF_ART",
                "page_num": [
                    15
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "2023",
                "label": "DATE",
                "page_num": [
                    15,
                    16,
                    17,
                    18
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "Nanyang Technological University",
                "label": "ORG",
                "page_num": [
                    15,
                    16,
                    17,
                    18
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "Singapore",
                "label": "GPE",
                "page_num": [
                    15,
                    16,
                    17,
                    18
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "15",
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "page_num": [
                    15
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "▪ Important",
                "label": "WORK_OF_ART",
                "page_num": [
                    16,
                    17
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "Unclear",
                "label": "WORK_OF_ART",
                "page_num": [
                    16
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "16",
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "page_num": [
                    16
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "Sequence of Prompts\n▪ Request",
                "label": "ORG",
                "page_num": [
                    17,
                    18
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "17",
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "page_num": [
                    17
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "18",
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "page_num": [
                    18
                ]
            }
        ],
        "Prompt Engineering Keys": [
            {
                "text": "▪ Define",
                "label": "PERSON",
                "page_num": [
                    19
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "AI",
                "label": "ORG",
                "page_num": [
                    19,
                    19,
                    19,
                    19
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "Specificity",
                "label": "ORG",
                "page_num": [
                    19
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "Detail",
                "label": "PERSON",
                "page_num": [
                    19
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "▪ Include",
                "label": "ORG",
                "page_num": [
                    19
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "Feedback Incorporation",
                "label": "ORG",
                "page_num": [
                    19
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "19",
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "page_num": [
                    19
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "2023",
                "label": "DATE",
                "page_num": [
                    19
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "Nanyang Technological University",
                "label": "ORG",
                "page_num": [
                    19
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "Singapore",
                "label": "GPE",
                "page_num": [
                    19
                ]
            }
        ],
        "Recommendation Chatbot": [
            {
                "text": "Recommendation Chatbot\nScenario\n▪",
                "label": "PERSON",
                "page_num": [
                    20
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "API",
                "label": "ORG",
                "page_num": [
                    20,
                    23,
                    25
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "2023",
                "label": "DATE",
                "page_num": [
                    20,
                    21,
                    22,
                    23,
                    24,
                    25
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "Nanyang Technological University",
                "label": "ORG",
                "page_num": [
                    20,
                    21,
                    22,
                    23,
                    24,
                    25
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "Singapore",
                "label": "GPE",
                "page_num": [
                    20,
                    21,
                    22,
                    23,
                    24,
                    25
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "20",
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "page_num": [
                    20
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "Recommendation Chatbot\nPrompt",
                "label": "PERSON",
                "page_num": [
                    21,
                    23
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "Server",
                "label": "ORG",
                "page_num": [
                    21,
                    22
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "21",
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "page_num": [
                    21
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "Recommendation Chatbot\n▪ For",
                "label": "ORG",
                "page_num": [
                    22
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "OpenAI",
                "label": "GPE",
                "page_num": [
                    22
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "API\n▪ The",
                "label": "ORG",
                "page_num": [
                    22
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "22",
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "page_num": [
                    22
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "Embedding\nUser-interface \n(",
                "label": "WORK_OF_ART",
                "page_num": [
                    23
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "▪ Customer",
                "label": "ORG",
                "page_num": [
                    23
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "Chatbot",
                "label": "PERSON",
                "page_num": [
                    23
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "23",
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "page_num": [
                    23
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "Recommendation Chatbot\nServer",
                "label": "PERSON",
                "page_num": [
                    24
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "first",
                "label": "ORDINAL",
                "page_num": [
                    24
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "24",
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "page_num": [
                    24
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "Recommendation Chatbot\nUser",
                "label": "PERSON",
                "page_num": [
                    25
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "25",
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "page_num": [
                    25
                ]
            }
        ],
        "Summary": [
            {
                "text": "NLP",
                "label": "ORG",
                "page_num": [
                    26
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "Applications\n▪ Fraud Detection Model\n▪ Human Trafficking Model",
                "label": "ORG",
                "page_num": [
                    26
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "Applications\n▪ Content Moderation\n▪ Product Recommendation Chatbot",
                "label": "ORG",
                "page_num": [
                    26
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "2023",
                "label": "DATE",
                "page_num": [
                    26
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "Nanyang Technological University",
                "label": "ORG",
                "page_num": [
                    26
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "Singapore",
                "label": "GPE",
                "page_num": [
                    26
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "26",
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "page_num": [
                    26
                ]
            }
        ]
    },
    "EE6405_W1_Introduction to NLP_For Students.pdf": {
        "EE6405": [
            {
                "text": "S. Supraja",
                "label": "PERSON",
                "page_num": [
                    1
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "NTU Electrical and Electronic Engineering",
                "label": "ORG",
                "page_num": [
                    1
                ]
            }
        ],
        "Content": [
            {
                "text": "Week",
                "label": "DATE",
                "page_num": [
                    2
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "1",
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "page_num": [
                    2
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "2",
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "page_num": [
                    2
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "3",
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "page_num": [
                    2
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "4",
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "page_num": [
                    2
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "5",
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "page_num": [
                    2
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "6",
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "page_num": [
                    2
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "7",
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "page_num": [
                    2
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "8",
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "page_num": [
                    2
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "9",
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "page_num": [
                    2
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "10",
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "page_num": [
                    2
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "11",
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "page_num": [
                    2
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "NLP",
                "label": "ORG",
                "page_num": [
                    2,
                    2,
                    2
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "Linguistic Feature Extraction\nTerm Weighting Schemes",
                "label": "ORG",
                "page_num": [
                    2
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "Neural Language Models\nTransformers\nHyperparameter Tuning\nTransformer",
                "label": "WORK_OF_ART",
                "page_num": [
                    2
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "Large Language Models",
                "label": "ORG",
                "page_num": [
                    2
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "NLP Applications\nTraditional \nMachine \nLearning\nDeep\nLearning\nNew NLP",
                "label": "WORK_OF_ART",
                "page_num": [
                    2
                ]
            }
        ],
        "Course Objectives": [
            {
                "text": "▪ Identify",
                "label": "WORK_OF_ART",
                "page_num": [
                    3
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "NLP",
                "label": "ORG",
                "page_num": [
                    3,
                    3,
                    3,
                    3,
                    4
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "▪ Execute",
                "label": "ORG",
                "page_num": [
                    3
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "▪ Implement NLP",
                "label": "ORG",
                "page_num": [
                    3
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "Python",
                "label": "GPE",
                "page_num": [
                    3
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "Distinguish",
                "label": "NORP",
                "page_num": [
                    3
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "4",
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "page_num": [
                    3
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "RNN",
                "label": "ORG",
                "page_num": [
                    4
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "5",
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "page_num": [
                    4
                ]
            }
        ],
        "Introduction to NLP": [
            {
                "text": "NLP",
                "label": "ORG",
                "page_num": [
                    5
                ]
            }
        ],
        "What is NLP?": [
            {
                "text": "NLP",
                "label": "ORG",
                "page_num": [
                    6,
                    6
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "Machine \nTranslation",
                "label": "ORG",
                "page_num": [
                    6
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "one",
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "page_num": [
                    6
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "7",
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "page_num": [
                    6
                ]
            }
        ],
        "NLP Around Us": [
            {
                "text": "NLP",
                "label": "ORG",
                "page_num": [
                    7
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "Us",
                "label": "GPE",
                "page_num": [
                    7
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "8",
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "page_num": [
                    7
                ]
            }
        ],
        "A Brief History of NLP": [
            {
                "text": "NLP",
                "label": "ORG",
                "page_num": [
                    8,
                    8,
                    8
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "1906",
                "label": "DATE",
                "page_num": [
                    8
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "Ferdinand de Saussure",
                "label": "ORG",
                "page_num": [
                    8
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "1916",
                "label": "DATE",
                "page_num": [
                    8
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "Cours de Linguistique Générale",
                "label": "ORG",
                "page_num": [
                    8
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "1957",
                "label": "DATE",
                "page_num": [
                    8
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "Noam Chomsky",
                "label": "PERSON",
                "page_num": [
                    8
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "1980s",
                "label": "DATE",
                "page_num": [
                    8
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "processing(symbolic",
                "label": "ORG",
                "page_num": [
                    8
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "models(stochastic",
                "label": "ORG",
                "page_num": [
                    8
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "1997",
                "label": "DATE",
                "page_num": [
                    8
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "2007",
                "label": "DATE",
                "page_num": [
                    8
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "2003",
                "label": "DATE",
                "page_num": [
                    8
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "Yoshio Bengio",
                "label": "NORP",
                "page_num": [
                    8
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "first",
                "label": "ORDINAL",
                "page_num": [
                    8,
                    8
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "2011",
                "label": "DATE",
                "page_num": [
                    8
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "Apple",
                "label": "ORG",
                "page_num": [
                    8
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "Siri",
                "label": "PERSON",
                "page_num": [
                    8
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "NLP/AI",
                "label": "ORG",
                "page_num": [
                    8
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "9",
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "page_num": [
                    8
                ]
            }
        ],
        "Approaches to NLP": [
            {
                "text": "NLP",
                "label": "ORG",
                "page_num": [
                    9,
                    9
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "Probabilistic \nlanguage",
                "label": "LANGUAGE",
                "page_num": [
                    9
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "Bayes Theorem",
                "label": "PERSON",
                "page_num": [
                    9
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "K-Means\nNeural",
                "label": "ORG",
                "page_num": [
                    9
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "BERT",
                "label": "ORG",
                "page_num": [
                    9
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "10",
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "page_num": [
                    9
                ]
            }
        ],
        "Preprocessing Techniques": [
            {
                "text": "TOKENIZATION\nBreak",
                "label": "FAC",
                "page_num": [
                    10
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "NORMALIZATION",
                "label": "LOC",
                "page_num": [
                    10
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "HANDLING OOV WORDS \nReplace",
                "label": "ORG",
                "page_num": [
                    10
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "subword",
                "label": "PERSON",
                "page_num": [
                    10
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "SENTENCE",
                "label": "PERSON",
                "page_num": [
                    10
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "FEATURE ENGINEERING\nExtract",
                "label": "ORG",
                "page_num": [
                    10
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "11",
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "page_num": [
                    10
                ]
            }
        ],
        "Preprocessing Techniques – RegEx": [
            {
                "text": "RegEx",
                "label": "ORG",
                "page_num": [
                    11,
                    12
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "Pomeranian",
                "label": "NORP",
                "page_num": [
                    11,
                    16
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "Pomeranians",
                "label": "NORP",
                "page_num": [
                    11
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "Sorry Prof",
                "label": "PERSON",
                "page_num": [
                    11
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "12",
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "page_num": [
                    11
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "Special Sequences",
                "label": "ORG",
                "page_num": [
                    12
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "\\",
                "label": "PERSON",
                "page_num": [
                    12
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "13",
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "page_num": [
                    12
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "Pattern\nMatches",
                "label": "PRODUCT",
                "page_num": [
                    16
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "pomeranian\npomeranian",
                "label": "NORP",
                "page_num": [
                    16
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "pomeranian$",
                "label": "ORG",
                "page_num": [
                    16
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "17",
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "page_num": [
                    16
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "18",
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "page_num": [
                    17
                ]
            }
        ],
        "Preprocessing Techniques – RegEx – Metacharacters": [
            {
                "text": "Character\nDescription",
                "label": "PRODUCT",
                "page_num": [
                    13
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "\\",
                "label": "PERSON",
                "page_num": [
                    13
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "Starts With\nEnds With\nZero",
                "label": "WORK_OF_ART",
                "page_num": [
                    13
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "One",
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "page_num": [
                    13
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "Zero",
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "page_num": [
                    13
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "one",
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "page_num": [
                    13
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "\\.",
                "label": "DATE",
                "page_num": [
                    13
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "14",
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "page_num": [
                    13
                ]
            }
        ],
        "Preprocessing Techniques – RegEx – Special Sequences": [
            {
                "text": "\\B\n\\d",
                "label": "PERSON",
                "page_num": [
                    14
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "\\D",
                "label": "ORG",
                "page_num": [
                    14,
                    14
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "\\s",
                "label": "ORG",
                "page_num": [
                    14
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "\\Z",
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "page_num": [
                    14
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "\\AThe",
                "label": "ORG",
                "page_num": [
                    14
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "0-9",
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "page_num": [
                    14,
                    14
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "Returns",
                "label": "PERSON",
                "page_num": [
                    14,
                    14
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "\\d",
                "label": "ORG",
                "page_num": [
                    14
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "\\w",
                "label": "WORK_OF_ART",
                "page_num": [
                    14
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "15",
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "page_num": [
                    14
                ]
            }
        ],
        "Preprocessing Techniques – RegEx – Sets": [
            {
                "text": "0",
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "page_num": [
                    15
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "one",
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "page_num": [
                    15
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "Returns",
                "label": "PERSON",
                "page_num": [
                    15,
                    15,
                    15
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "EXCEPT",
                "label": "ORG",
                "page_num": [
                    15
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "1",
                "label": "DATE",
                "page_num": [
                    15
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "2",
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "page_num": [
                    15
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "3",
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "page_num": [
                    15
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "between 0-9",
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "page_num": [
                    15
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "two",
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "page_num": [
                    15
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "00",
                "label": "DATE",
                "page_num": [
                    15
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "59",
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "page_num": [
                    15
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "16",
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "page_num": [
                    15
                ]
            }
        ],
        "Preprocessing Techniques – NLTK": [
            {
                "text": "Natural Language Toolkit",
                "label": "WORK_OF_ART",
                "page_num": [
                    18
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "API",
                "label": "ORG",
                "page_num": [
                    18
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "NLP",
                "label": "ORG",
                "page_num": [
                    18
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "▪ Contains",
                "label": "ORG",
                "page_num": [
                    18
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "▪ Examples",
                "label": "WORK_OF_ART",
                "page_num": [
                    18
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "Tokenization\nStop",
                "label": "ORG",
                "page_num": [
                    18
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "Lemmatization/",
                "label": "GPE",
                "page_num": [
                    18
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "19",
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "page_num": [
                    18
                ]
            }
        ],
        "Preprocessing Techniques – Tokenization": [
            {
                "text": "subwords(n-gram",
                "label": "LAW",
                "page_num": [
                    19
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "20",
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "page_num": [
                    19
                ]
            }
        ],
        "Preprocessing Techniques – Stemming": [
            {
                "text": "21",
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "page_num": [
                    20
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "▪ Grouping",
                "label": "PERSON",
                "page_num": [
                    21
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "▪ Language Challenges",
                "label": "WORK_OF_ART",
                "page_num": [
                    21
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "French",
                "label": "LANGUAGE",
                "page_num": [
                    21
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "English",
                "label": "LANGUAGE",
                "page_num": [
                    21
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "22",
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "page_num": [
                    21
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "23",
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "page_num": [
                    22
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "Dumbledore",
                "label": "PERSON",
                "page_num": [
                    23
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "Snape",
                "label": "NORP",
                "page_num": [
                    23
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "Snape",
                "label": "ORG",
                "page_num": [
                    23
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "silveri",
                "label": "NORP",
                "page_num": [
                    23
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "24",
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "page_num": [
                    23
                ]
            }
        ],
        "Preprocessing Techniques – Lemmatization": [
            {
                "text": "Lemmatization\nStudy\n▪ As",
                "label": "WORK_OF_ART",
                "page_num": [
                    24
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "25",
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "page_num": [
                    24
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "Lemmatization",
                "label": "PRODUCT",
                "page_num": [
                    25
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "26",
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "page_num": [
                    25
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "27",
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "page_num": [
                    26
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "28",
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "page_num": [
                    27
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "Dumbledore",
                "label": "PERSON",
                "page_num": [
                    28,
                    28
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "Snape",
                "label": "NORP",
                "page_num": [
                    28
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "Snape",
                "label": "ORG",
                "page_num": [
                    28,
                    28,
                    28
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "29",
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "page_num": [
                    28
                ]
            }
        ],
        "Preprocessing Techniques – BOW": [
            {
                "text": "Bag-Of-Words",
                "label": "WORK_OF_ART",
                "page_num": [
                    29
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "▪ Considered a ‘bag’",
                "label": "WORK_OF_ART",
                "page_num": [
                    29
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "▪ Converts",
                "label": "ORG",
                "page_num": [
                    29
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "30",
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "page_num": [
                    29
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "Worked Example\nSentence 1",
                "label": "WORK_OF_ART",
                "page_num": [
                    30,
                    31,
                    32
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "2",
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "page_num": [
                    30,
                    30,
                    31,
                    31,
                    32,
                    32,
                    32,
                    32,
                    32,
                    33,
                    33
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "1",
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "page_num": [
                    30,
                    30,
                    32,
                    32,
                    32,
                    32,
                    32,
                    32,
                    32,
                    32,
                    33
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "31",
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "page_num": [
                    30
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "32",
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "page_num": [
                    31
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "3",
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "page_num": [
                    32
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "7",
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "page_num": [
                    32,
                    32
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "one",
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "page_num": [
                    32
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "Frequency",
                "label": "ORG",
                "page_num": [
                    32,
                    32
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "0",
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "page_num": [
                    32,
                    32,
                    32,
                    32
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "33",
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "page_num": [
                    32
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "Worked Example\nCosine Distance/Similarity",
                "label": "ORG",
                "page_num": [
                    33
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "2,2,2,1,1,0,0",
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "page_num": [
                    33
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "1,1,1,0,0,1,1",
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "page_num": [
                    33
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "One",
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "page_num": [
                    33
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "34",
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "page_num": [
                    33
                ]
            }
        ],
        "Preprocessing Techniques – N-grams": [
            {
                "text": "The ‘n’ in n-grams",
                "label": "WORK_OF_ART",
                "page_num": [
                    34
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "Bigram",
                "label": "PRODUCT",
                "page_num": [
                    34
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "Trigram",
                "label": "PERSON",
                "page_num": [
                    34
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "35",
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "page_num": [
                    34
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "▪ N-grams",
                "label": "ORG",
                "page_num": [
                    35
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "1",
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "page_num": [
                    35,
                    37,
                    37,
                    37,
                    37
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "2",
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "page_num": [
                    35,
                    35,
                    37,
                    37,
                    37,
                    37,
                    37,
                    37,
                    37,
                    37
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "3",
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "page_num": [
                    35,
                    35,
                    37,
                    37,
                    37
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "4",
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "page_num": [
                    35,
                    35
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "5",
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "page_num": [
                    35
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "𝑊𝑊\n𝑃𝑃\n1",
                "label": "PRODUCT",
                "page_num": [
                    35
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "𝑃𝑃 𝐵𝐵",
                "label": "ORG",
                "page_num": [
                    35
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "𝐵𝐵",
                "label": "NORP",
                "page_num": [
                    35,
                    35
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "𝑃𝑃 𝐴𝐴",
                "label": "ORG",
                "page_num": [
                    35
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "𝑃𝑃 𝐵𝐵",
                "label": "PERSON",
                "page_num": [
                    35
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "𝐶𝐶",
                "label": "ORG",
                "page_num": [
                    35
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "𝐵𝐵\n𝐵𝐵\n𝐵𝐵\n𝐵𝐵\n𝐴𝐴\n",
                "label": "PERSON",
                "page_num": [
                    35
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "36",
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "page_num": [
                    35
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "the Markov Assumption",
                "label": "ORG",
                "page_num": [
                    36
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "− 𝑈𝑈𝑛𝑛𝑈𝑈𝑈𝑈𝑜𝑜𝑈𝑈𝑈𝑈",
                "label": "PERSON",
                "page_num": [
                    36
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "− 𝐵𝐵𝑈𝑈𝑈𝑈𝑜𝑜𝑈𝑈𝑈𝑈\n▪ Intuitively",
                "label": "PERSON",
                "page_num": [
                    36
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "37",
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "page_num": [
                    36
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "Worked Example\n𝑃𝑃 𝑤𝑤𝑖𝑖 𝑤𝑤𝑖𝑖−1 =\n𝑐𝑐(𝑤𝑤𝑖𝑖−1",
                "label": "WORK_OF_ART",
                "page_num": [
                    37
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "0.67 𝑃𝑃 𝐼𝐼 < 𝑇𝑇",
                "label": "QUANTITY",
                "page_num": [
                    37
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "0.33",
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "page_num": [
                    37
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "𝑈𝑈𝑇𝑇",
                "label": "GPE",
                "page_num": [
                    37
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "1 𝑃𝑃",
                "label": "TIME",
                "page_num": [
                    37
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "0.5",
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "page_num": [
                    37,
                    37
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "0.67",
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "page_num": [
                    37
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "38",
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "page_num": [
                    37
                ]
            }
        ],
        "Summary": [
            {
                "text": "this week",
                "label": "DATE",
                "page_num": [
                    38,
                    39
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "▪ Preprocessing",
                "label": "WORK_OF_ART",
                "page_num": [
                    38
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "RegEx",
                "label": "ORG",
                "page_num": [
                    38
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "39",
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "page_num": [
                    38
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "Bag of Words",
                "label": "WORK_OF_ART",
                "page_num": [
                    39
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "Contiguous",
                "label": "GPE",
                "page_num": [
                    39
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "40",
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "page_num": [
                    39
                ]
            }
        ]
    },
    "EE6405_W2_Linguistic Analysis and Information Extraction_For Students.pdf": {
        "EE6405": [
            {
                "text": "S. Supraja",
                "label": "PERSON",
                "page_num": [
                    1
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "NTU Electrical and Electronic Engineering",
                "label": "ORG",
                "page_num": [
                    1
                ]
            }
        ],
        "Linguistic Analysis and": [
            {
                "text": "Linguistic Analysis",
                "label": "ORG",
                "page_num": [
                    2
                ]
            }
        ],
        "Information Extraction": [
            {
                "text": "Information Extraction\nInformation Extraction Systems",
                "label": "ORG",
                "page_num": [
                    3
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "▪ Locate",
                "label": "ORG",
                "page_num": [
                    3
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "▪ Summarise",
                "label": "PERSON",
                "page_num": [
                    3
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "▪ Produce",
                "label": "PERSON",
                "page_num": [
                    3
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "Unstructured Data",
                "label": "ORG",
                "page_num": [
                    3
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "AP",
                "label": "ORG",
                "page_num": [
                    3
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "72 yo f",
                "label": "QUANTITY",
                "page_num": [
                    3
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "CAD",
                "label": "ORG",
                "page_num": [
                    3
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "pw/",
                "label": "ORG",
                "page_num": [
                    3
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "72 years old",
                "label": "DATE",
                "page_num": [
                    3
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "3",
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "page_num": [
                    3
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "Information Extraction\nGoals:\nInformation \nOrganisation",
                "label": "ORG",
                "page_num": [
                    4
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "Structured Data",
                "label": "ORG",
                "page_num": [
                    4
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "4",
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "page_num": [
                    4
                ]
            }
        ],
        "Named Entity Recognition (NER)": [
            {
                "text": "NER",
                "label": "ORG",
                "page_num": [
                    5,
                    5,
                    6,
                    6,
                    6,
                    7,
                    7,
                    8,
                    8,
                    11,
                    12
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "Named Entity Recognition",
                "label": "WORK_OF_ART",
                "page_num": [
                    5
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "▪ Works",
                "label": "ORG",
                "page_num": [
                    5
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "▪ Delivers",
                "label": "ORG",
                "page_num": [
                    5
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "5",
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "page_num": [
                    5
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "▪ Eg: Google",
                "label": "WORK_OF_ART",
                "page_num": [
                    6
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "Tolkien",
                "label": "ORG",
                "page_num": [
                    6
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "6",
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "page_num": [
                    6
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "▪ Organisations\n▪ Locations\n▪ Dates\n▪ Persons\n▪ Events\n▪ These",
                "label": "WORK_OF_ART",
                "page_num": [
                    7
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "7",
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "page_num": [
                    7
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "two",
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "page_num": [
                    8
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "United Overseas \nBank",
                "label": "ORG",
                "page_num": [
                    8
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "three",
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "page_num": [
                    8
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "8",
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "page_num": [
                    8
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "11",
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "page_num": [
                    11
                ]
            },
            {
                "text": "12",
                "label": "CARDINAL",
                "page_num": [
                    12
                ]
            }
        ],
        "Named Entity Recognition – Using spaCy": [
            {
                "text": "SpaCy",
                "label": "PERSON",
